Of, so right now we are good here,
and Mark has been also working very,
very closely with the progress of these
dashboards.
I know Y.T.
and Umar has been discussing some council,
so to following up about the requirements,
test it.
Yeah,
we are we are kind of eager to have a
first look how how it's going to look
like, so,
so Mark said that they have some initial
look at the dashboard he can go over with,
so...
Mhm.
Yeah.
That's good watching.
Based on the requirement that Nimbo,
Nirmala and I provided, yeah.
Mhm.
So.
Sorry,
I have some issues with my PC today.
But yeah,
and that's the idea for today's call is
to form it up about the collateral
release dashboard that is already on
Mm.
production. And then WaiChee,
we need to discuss this one with Nirmala
and you,
because I know that on the part of the
Mm.
collateral release dashboard,
it's one you're one of the stakeholders
that's forming up on this dashboard and
also
Okay,
so let's start making the UAT testing for
this week. Sorry,
I cannot share right now the project
Okay.
scale, but I will share in the mini notes.
And then after that part, it's like,
Yeah.
let's start the UAT testing for next week.
After we have the next week already done
with the requirements,
Mm.
then we can make the complete go live on
September 1. That would be the plan.
Let's scale for that.
So,
that's for the that's for collateral for
the collateral dashboard, right? Is it?
Yeah, correct. The collateral attachment.
So, collateral test brought UAT next week,
right? What we,
which is what week thirty-five, right?
Mhm.
And then release the production.
It's.
Yes,
after we have already your agreement that
Wu.
we are okay with that collateral in case
that you doesn't need anything else,
any graph,
so we can make a go live in September 1
that is a work week 36.
Okay, so I'll be off next week,
but let me ask Vijay who should be in the
UAT. But all right.
Thank you.
Sounds good. Yeah, please let me know.
In case not, it's not you,
All right.
probably Nirmala will help us there.
Nirmala will be available.
Yes.
Yes,
I think normally collateral is released
by Limala's group,
so they should be the key one,
but from the from FTS now we are caught
with the new organization.
If you don't know,
we are called Customer Engineering Group.
So, this is a new group name for us,
so just...
Hey, hi, uh, Nirmala has asked to record.
I don't think it's recording.
Okay, yen.
And there's something right now,
but when we start the dashboard
presentation, we can start recording,
start recording.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, thank you.
No, thank you, WaiChee.
Thank you for that information. Mark,
M.
make sense for this point?
Sorry, repeat. What was the statement?
It's to, yep,
make the UAD testing next week and then
go live the collateral release on
September 1. That is the word with 36.
Okay, yeah, I think that's fine.
Yeah, and after this,
I'll send a note to both Nirmala and
Great.
Vijay. I believe Nirmala will be,
you know, one of the UAT.
Yep.
Uh, and then, uh,
we will provide some a name to represent
Ops.
M.T.S. Alright, thank you.
Good. No, thank you.
Perfect. Let's go from the next one.
Sorry,
I cannot share because my computer is
very slow and in case that I share,
Mm.
it's completely losing audio.
But the second dashboard,
it's about the internal internal
collateral.
Yes.
No internal Jira tickets, okay?
Actually,
I'm not sure why we call it internal.
Basically, it's external ticket system,
right?
So these are the ticket dashboard that we
want to monitor and track the tickets
that's issued.
From by the customer or on behalf of the
customer, so it is external to me,
but I'm...
It is external.
So, yeah, to me it's external, right? So,
so I'm not sure what, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah,
I think that should be the right name.
It should be the external dashboard.
Internal is separate.
That's the one for the DTP migration
right here.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, on that one that we have...
It's.
On that one, it's like, again,
the DTP data is the one that is from
external. That's right.
DTP should be internal.
DTP will should be internal, okay?
So, so, so, so maybe,
maybe I just want to refresh,
but can I share just one sec? OK.
Yes, please.
To where is that?
Can you see this right?
Yes.
So, so she is speaking now.
Do you see this diagram?
Yes, we can.
Is there a way to zoom in on it? Oh, okay,
there we go. Thank you.
Well, okay.
So, so,
so I'm talking about this ticket here,
right? So,
right now there are two dashboards, right?
And there's a firewall here,
whatever we call it, right?
And these are two instances, right? We,
I have, we,
I have my own dashboard mode tracking all
the Jira tickets coming in, OK? And then..
.